export const Questions = [
  {
    question: "Who was the first Straw Hat to be shown in the anime?",
    options: ["Luffy", "Zoro", "Nami", "Usopp"],
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "What was the first ever named attack used by Luffy?",

    options: [
      "Gum-Gum Rocket",
      "Gum-Gum Bullet",
      "Gum-Gum Gatling",
      "Gum-Gum Pistol",
    ],
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Where was Gol D. Roger executed?",
    options: ["Raftel", "Loguetown", "Goa Kingdom", "Gray Terminal"],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "In which arc was Franky's hair a cannon?",
    options: ["Zou", "Fishman Island", "Dressrosa", "Wano"],
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "What was the Luffy's first bounty?",
    options: [
      "15,000,000 Berries",
      "30,000,000 Berries",
      "20,000,000 Berries",
      "40,000,000 Berries",
    ],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Who took over Chopper's body in Punk Hazard?",
    options: ["Franky", "Sanji", "Nami", "Usopp"],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Where was the first Road Poneglph located that the Straw Hats found?",
    options: ["Fishman Island", "Zou", "Wholecake Island", "Wano"],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Who could not only listen, but communicate with Zunesha?",
    options: ["Momonosuke", "Luffy", "Inuarashi", "Nekomamushi"],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What was Luffy's bounty after the Whole cake island?",
    options: [
      "500,000,000 Berries",
      "1,000,000,000 Berries",
      "1,500,000,000 Berries",
      "2,000,000,000 Berries",
    ],
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the only race/tribe you can't find on tottoland as mentioned in the arc?",
    options: ["Mink Tribe", "Giants", "Three-Eye Tribe", "Longleg Tribe"],
    answer: 2,
  },
];
